I don't know what you're
saying I'm thinking about
it I'm trying to say
happy end You're not clear,
you're not clear I'm feeling
real I hope you're who,
I hope you're who
Hey,
you're not a future, you're not
a future I hope you're who you,
you hope you're who you
I hope you're who you,
I hope you're who you
Thank you so much for watching.
Magic is a cutting-edge
field of study in this world,
like Revolution's version of IT.
It's such a big deal here that a country's
political standing depends
on how well they use it.
Note, students,
that magic stones like this one are
the foundation of every magic tool.
This magic wand, for example, was crafted
with a magic stone at the top. In fact,
it was the stones that inspired early
mages to invent the magic tools we use.
Today's magic wielders can bring about all
sorts of phenomena depending
upon their strength.
The greater and purer one's talent is, the
greater the wonders they're capable of.
Of course, mining and distribution of
magic stones is nationally regulated.
In this nation,
they are managed by the Aurousseau Company
with the permission of the royal family.
As an aside, that's my Linnaeus household.
Now, during today's lesson, practice
firing magic shots with your wands.
Your targets will represent monsters.
Try to envision them.
Wait, there's more!
These stones are the reason there's
monsters running around in the first place.
The monsters were normal
animals until they
decided to shove the
stones down their gullets.
Now they're all buffed up and terrifying!
You want to get rid of a monster, you
have to remove and destroy the stone.
Right then.
Really, Ray?
Every time I look over at
you, you're spacing out.
What's going on with you?
Oh, nothing, really.
Just daydreaming.
Nothing, indeed.
I understand this may be review for you,
but even a dual caster
needs to practice every day.
Yeah, you're right.
Let's see.
Sure, I can do a magic shot.
Bibbidi-bubbidi-boosh.
Oh!
Wow.
I always wonder what was so
great about dual casters.
Oh crap, I overshot or over-strengthened?
Why am I like this?
I'm officially too OP to function!
That's getting a bit
overconfident, commoner.
You're a fool.
It doesn't take a dual
caster to pull that off.
I don't know what to say.
Your tears of frustration
speak for themselves.
They're tears of awe.
Will you marry me?
What?
Where'd that come from?
Ladies, please, don't lose focus.
Oh, Professor Torrid.
Magic can be fun, but it's a very
dangerous art if used incorrectly.
Please be sure to conduct
yourselves with caution.
Okay, sorry.
I apologize, sir.
May I help you?
I'm so impressed.
You may be a noble,
but you're still able
to show true respect to
someone who's in a position
of authority over you.
A lady after my own heart.
Of course I respect him.
Professor Torrid was
one of the pioneers who
established the foundations
of magic in this kingdom.
Though his ability is ranked intermediate,
he commands the attributes of fire,
earth, and water, thus making him the
kingdom's one and only Tri-Caster.
I hope this is not news.
Even commoners should know that.
Rest assured, this commoner is aware.
Our kingdom's magic was quite unimpressive
until Professor Torrid
laid down some moves.
All hail the mother of magic!
Whatever you're doing,
stop at this instant.
You're making a public
spectacle of yourself.
I'm not with them.
Moving on.
It is important to be familiar
with the four attributes.
Every elemental attribute has a
different element that it can counter.
Earth is strong against wind.
Wind is strong against water,
fire is strong against earth,
and water is strong against fire.
Of course, it doesn't always
work exactly like that.
There are some exceptions.
Make note, there are other ways in
which the attributes can be categorized.
For example, you can use
earth magic to defend.
Walls may be created
out of earth like this.
Advanced users can work on a larger scale,
crafting walls that
would fortify a castle.
Conversely, fire magic
attacks and water magic heals.
It can be used to treat
injuries and illnesses.
However, water can never be used
to bring the dead back to life.
Now for our final attribute,
wind magic, which I cannot wield,
is used in supportive roles.
Combining wind magic with fire
increases its attack power.
while combining it with water
increases its healing capabilities.
And end tutorial. All right.
If there are no questions, then
let's put this into practice.
If you have a wind attribute, come see me.
I will be working with you individually.
An earth wall, huh?
Okay, not a big deal.
It warms my heart to see how
close you two have become.
Prince Rod! Prince Yu!
If you believe I have any kind of
relationship with that ridiculous girl,
and I'm afraid you're gratefully mistaken.
Who are you aware of this?
Her hatred keeps things spicy between us.
Will you please shut up?
Anyway, where's uh prince? Then?
Oh, him.
He's over there with
professor toward you.
Really destroyed that target earlier.
Well done.
We've never been great at magic
ourselves so please forgive us.
We truly admire your skill. Okay.
Their Highness just deigned to praise you.
Are you not grateful?
I mean, it's nice.
But your praise is what
my heart truly desires.
See, practically joined at the hip.
Which reminds me.
Are you two ladies planning to take the
academy knights exam together next week?
Come on, rod.
Why would ray know anything
about the academy knights?
Oh, you have a point there.
Well then, allow me to
give you the rundown.
The Academy Knights resolve
conflicts between students,
kill monsters on the grounds,
that kind of thing.
They're a self-governed
organization within the Academy.
It's deeply rooted in tradition, and only
the elite who pass the exam can join.
I think it would be well
worth your while to try.
Wow, that's really interesting.
I know about the Knights.
I mean, they were in the
game, so why wouldn't I?
They go by the name knights, but
it's basically the student council.
If you join, you get to see some
exclusive event CGs of the Princes.
Which is no big whoop for me, so
I really didn't care if I got in.
You don't seem very enthused right now.
I figured you of all people would
jump at the chance to join up.
Um, yeah, I don't know.
Imagine getting to say, Back Fiend, I'm
the knight who protects Miss Claire!
I can't be Miss Claire's knight?
It's a villain!
Someone please save me! My lady!
Are you all right?
I am now.
Thank you, my knight.
I will not ask what that was all about,
as I'm certain I'll be horrified.
But of course I will be
taking the exam as well.
And as a knight, I hardly think
I'll need your protection.
Wait, that's even better!
Put me down this instant!
I won't have someone protecting
me for the rest of my life!
Lady or not, I know how to fight.
I know that look saves
your first thoughts!
Anyone else feel that shaking?
Uh, what is that? An earthquake?
A monster!
Take cover!
It's a monster attack!
That looks like a water slime.
Yeah, and a huge one, too.
If they were to make contact,
there's no way we would survive.
Get back, everyone!
Hurry and find refuge
while I take care of this!
Move back!
Try to stay calm! This way! Almost there!
Commoner, this is no time for your danger.
We need to get out of here.
Wait!
Miss Taylor, what do
you think you're doing?
That monster's a water type.
We need wind magic to defeat it, and
it's not one of your attributes, is it?
I'll manage some other way.
Trust me, I can help.
How did you manage to construct such
advanced magic walls so quickly?
You're not a novice caster, are you?
You got it, Pops.
I ain't no noob.
This is a monster attack
that happens in the game.
I knew this was coming,
and I have been racking up my
magic skills so I can slay all day.
Took a little getting used to,
but it's nothing I can't handle.
Thanks to my sweet, sweet protags, Bix.
It's weak enough to
overpower with numbers now.
Tell everyone to turn around and attack.
Right, I shall.
Students, when I give the signal, I
need everyone to use their attack magic.
Be sure to aim through the cracks.
Between the earth walls?
Fire!
No, false.
All we did was set a flag.
Try to keep your ears covered.
Monsters do this to threaten foes.
It's called the hateful pride.
Damn it! I can't move!
I won't fight!
Not good!
Even Prince Rod and Prince,
you are immobilized!
Are you sure we're not
supposed to let that happen?
Oh no!
I must have used up all
my magic on those walls!
Crap, it's happening!
This is about to end up just
like it does in the game!
The whole point of this stupid event is to
place the stupid heroine in stupid danger!
Only for her to be rescued
by one of the stupid princes!
Wait a minute, is that what I think it is?
No!
I don't want to choose a prince!
It'll set a freaking flag!
Whoever I pick, it'll level
up their affection for me!
I need an option that's
not one of the princes!
Some other name to call.
And if I had my way, I
know which one it would be!
Save me!
Miss Claire!
That's right, I forgot.
Miss Claire's also been caught
by a tentacle in this scene.
She shows up in Prince Dane's event CG.
It's a super tiny image of
her, but still breathtaking.
Miss Claire, no!
Could this monster be any more barbaric?
That hateful cry was so hateful.
I fear I'm in no condition to be of help.
Please stay strong, Claire Francois.
Oh, Prince Tain, it's you!
I shall support you.
Hit that monster with all
the magic at your disposal!
Well, I would.
But my attribute is fire.
So I don't think it will do
much good against a water type.
Yes, it will.
I believe in you.
All right.
Be sure to hit it with full power.
Is there any other way?
Not this time, not this girl!
You caught me off guard, but never again!
Is that an angel I see?
Or is that Miss Claire coming to save me?
I know you can do it, Miss Claire!
Roar forth!
Clad in the breeze.
Leave us!
Enchant, win!
Are you all right?
I apologize, your highness.
No, it's...
My bones.
Such incredible work, Ms.
Glenn!
I can't believe you took out that
enormous monster on your own in one hit!
But, I didn't do it on my own. I…
Ah, there you are.
It's okay.
You don't need to be afraid of me.
Come here.
That was your mommy in that
battle back there, huh?
And she was fighting to
protect you, wasn't she?
I am so sorry.
How about if I become your mommy
for a little while? It's okay.
We've forged the familiar pact.
I think I'll call you Ray Lair.
Hello there, Ray Lair.
Hey, this tickles!
Prince Thane!
I am...
I wanted to say how grateful I am.
I don't know what would have
happened if it weren't for you.
Thank you for helping me.
You're welcome, but you're quite skilled.
You would have survived without me.
Oh, I'm not so sure.
Even so...
It was well done.
You! Commoner!
Where did you run off to?
Are you alright?
Let me look, did it hurt you?
Uh oh no I'm just dandy but what about
you was that really the best idea?
pardon what are you talking about?
well you set the flag then for some
reason you went and snapped it in half.
this is not an appropriate
time for your nonsense!
do you know how worried I was about you?
the day has arrived.
you're finally showing affection to me!
silence!
you're delusional!
where do you even get
such ridiculous ideas!
Look, you did quite well
for a commoner. Huh?
What I mean is, thank you for
keeping that monster in one place.
I very much appreciate it.
Come on, Ray!
You too, Miss Claire!
Let's return to class, shall we?
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah
Ah, I'm really too late.
I'm going to take a break.
What is it?
What is it? What is it?
You can't stand there.
It's just a surprise.
Oh, you can't wait.
I'm not even close.
I'm not close.
Get away.
I'm going to get you.
What is it?
Why do you see me?
Why can't I turn to the camera?
That's a way you say.
You're looking at me.
What do you do, you're looking at me?
It's time to get out of the camera.
I'm not even going to
get out of the camera.
Let's go out of the camera.
We're going to do it.
I'm gonna take a look at the camera.
If I turn to the camera.
I'm looking at the camera.
I'm going to take a look at the camera.
I'm going to go out of the camera.
Really? You are not!
It's my wonderland
Just a sec, I'm sure I
have something for you.
Oh, who's a hungry little baby?
Whoa, wait! Ah!
Easy there, everyone.
You'll have plenty of time
to explore the world soon.
You've got to finish growing now.
What is that?
It's a monster.
Isn't it?
Ah!
Screamisha!
Just calm down and
listen to me, all right?
I'm as calm as I can be right now.
I need your help training
this little friend I made.
They're asking me to train a monster
as though we're discussing homework.
Ah, damn it!
It's really cute. Yes!
Thankfully, we won Misha over
with the power of cuteness,
and she helped me start a training
regimen for Little Ray Lair.
But...
Commoner, there you are.
Do you know where you
placed my hairbrush earlier?
Lene was looking for...
Uh-huh.
Ah.
That is a monster.
The first part of the night
exam is the written part.
This will be easy.
I've heard it's the norm
to always get answers
off by one when filling these things out.
Who is norm? As in normal?
Are you referring to me?
Why don't we compare our
answers, Miss Claire?